nice to meet you.
初めまして
It's so cute.
めちゃめちゃ可愛いですね
I'm surprised at how cute it is.
ちょっと可愛すぎてびっくりしてます
Are you someone from the entertainment industry?
芸能関係の方だったりします?
I'm a near idol and I'm aiming to become an idol.
私は近イドルでちゃんとアイドルを目指してます
Ah, that's right.
あ、やっぱそうっすよね
I thought it was that cute.
それぐらい可愛いなと思って
Is it already the wrong way to make a major debut?
もうメジャーデビュー逆道ですか?
not at all.
全然
You'll definitely sell.
あなた絶対売れるわよ
There's no doubt that I'll do it.
俺がやったら間違いないよ
I'm an idol.
アイドルさんなんだ
Do you actually like idols?
実際アイドルは好きなの?
I like it.
好きです
Try it yourself.
自分でやってみて
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
That's right.
そうだよね
But from now on, I'll be an idol, etc.
でもこれからもさ、アイドルとかでさ、
If it sells well, if it appears on TV or something, you'll be photographed a lot.
もし売れたらね、 テレビとかに出たらいっぱい撮られるよ
If you get too close to it, it's so cute that I can't stand it with this camera.
あまり近づくと可愛すぎて、 このカメラが耐えられないんで、
Just about this distance.
ちょっとこれぐらいの距離で
Oh, wait a minute.
あ、ちょっと待って
It was so cute that the camera was drawn to it.
ちょっと可愛すぎて、 カメラが吸い寄せられた
Even though she's cute, I'm drawn to her.
可愛いのいいのに吸い込まれてる
Sorry, sorry.
ごめんごめん
You know what you're going to do.
どういうことするかっていうのは分かってるよね
picture?
え?
What do you do?
どういうことするの?
tell me.
教えて
What do you photograph with this camera?
ここのカメラでどういうことを撮るの?
I'll just say it.
ちょっと言っちゃうな
What?
なんて?
Don't listen to it one by one.
聞きずつならねえ
What the hell?
なんてなんて?
Tell me again.
もう一回教えて
I'll just say it.
ちょっと言っちゃうな
various.
いろいろ
various?
いろいろ?
That's no good.
ダメじゃん
It would be better to call you a manager.
なんかマネージャーっていう方がいいですね
It's not something to get angry about.
怒るとするものじゃないね
By lottery.
くじで
Do the members know?
メンバーの子は知ってるの?
I don't know at all.
全然知らない
Well, the fact that you came to this place somehow...
まあでもなんかこういうとこに来てくれたってことは、
Even though I'm still in love, my eyes haven't opened yet.
まだやっぱり愛のうちでも、 まだ目が開いてないっていうか
There are words I really want to convey.
僕はどうしても伝えたい言葉があって
Oh, where did you just look?
あ、今どこ見た?
I don't think I've been there.
行ってないみたい
Huh?
あれ?
I just said there was something I wanted to tell you,
伝えたいことがあるって言っただけなのに、
I just scooted up a bit.
今、 ちょっとスクート立ったけどさ
Where did you just look?
今どこ見た?
I haven't been there.
行ってない
Oh, look.
あ、ほら
Also.
また
Are you watching this?
これ見てるんでしょ
You saw this, right?
これ見たんでしょ
I saw it.
見た
What's going on?
どうなってんすか?
I can see it.
見れてる
Are you having a handshake event?
握手会とかしてる?
Are you doing it?
してる?
A handshake event.
握手会とか
I think all the people lining up for the handshake event are like this.
握手会で並んでる人たち全員、 こんなこうなってると思う
Is it happening?
なってるのかな?
I think it's happening.
なってると思う
copper?
どう?
Honestly, just talking to you right now makes me so angry,
率直に今喋ってるだけで、 こんなガッとなってるけど、
What is your honest opinion?
率直にどう意見を?
I'd like you to consider me a fan and have a quick handshake.
俺をファンだと思ってさ、 ちょっと握手会してほしいんだけど
Is it good?
いいすか?
Well, about two people will come.
じゃあ、2人くらい来るから
About three people will come.
3人くらい来るから
thank you.
ありがとう
I'm always rooting for you.
いつも応援してます
thank you.
ありがとう
good luck.
頑張ってね
thank you.
ありがとう
I'm rooting for you.
応援してます
everytime.
いつも
Your hands are soft.
手、柔らかいっすね
soft.
柔らかい
thank you.
ありがとう
Can't you go a little longer?
もうちょっと行けんじゃないの?
please.
お願いします
picture?
え?
I won't.
しないよ
My hair is so sunny.
めちゃめちゃ髪太陽じゃん
You touched me though.
触ってくれたけど
Do you always have fans like that?
いつもそういうファンさしてるの?
not present.
いない
Usually, with those cute hands,
普段じゃあさ、その可愛い手でさ、
What do you hold when you idle?
アイドルしたときは何を握っているの?
Half correct.
半分正解
That's only half correct.
半分正解なんですけど
Then let me tell you.
じゃあ俺に教えてあげようか
penis.
おちんちん
Something I have to say.
言わなきゃいけないやつ
Even if you say something like that, don't pick up on the sound.
そんな感じで言われても、 音拾えないで
You can't pick it up.
拾えないでしょ
I couldn't pick it up, so I looked at the camera properly.
拾えてなかったから、ちゃんとカメラ見てやって
Hey, dick.
ねえ、おちんちん
You picked it up, right?
拾えたでしょ
penis.
おちんちん
So now it was my penis,
じゃあ今のは、 俺のおちんちんだったけど、
Do you have a penis?
おちんちんついてる?
It's not on.
ついてない
Tell me it's not there.
ついてないって言ってよ
I don't know.
わかんない
What do you say?
なんて言うんだろ
Shall I tell you?
教えてあげようか
Tell me.
教えてよ
I have to say it.
言わなきゃ
forget?
忘れる?
Yes, let's go to the actual performance.
はい、本番行きまーす
So, I'm going to take a naughty photo shoot today.
っていう感じで、 今日エッチな撮影するからね
Always so cute.
いつもはね、かわいい
Just ask me something else.
ちょっとだけ別のこと聞いて
What do you usually do?
普段は何をされてるのか?
nice.
いいね
What?
何が?
What year are you in?
何年生ですか?
I'm a second year student.
2年生です
Is it fun?
楽しいですか?
Is this what you're saying?
こう言ってんすか?
I wish I could say that.
言えたらいいですけど
I don't give it out.
出さない
What can I say?
何言える?
Oh yeah.
ああ、そうそう
I don't give it out.
出さない
oh yeah.
そうそう
If you could even tell me what kind of subject you studied, or even what department.
何系勉強というか、 学部とかまで言えたら
It's tough, being an idol.
大変だよね、アイドルの
That means it's done.
できてるってことっすよね
But,
でもさ、
Is the battery better than before?
昔 よりバッテリーか
It's a common thing.
よくあるやつね
A common one.
よくあるやつ
I mean, which department store?
つまり、 どこのデパートですか?
Don't tell me that.
それは内緒で
Is that a secret?
それは内緒?
Because it's definitely not going to happen.
絶対いかないから
Don't tell me that.
それは内緒で
Don't tell me.
内緒で
I had some hobbies.
趣味とかはあったですよ
What is your good night?
おやすみの日は?
Do you lie or something?
おなりとかはする?
be on one's mind?
気になる?
Because it's a special symbol.
特命記号だから
That's fine, that's right.
いいんよ、そんね
I think I'm closer than any other fan right now.
俺今、どのファンよりも近いんじゃない?
carry.
キャリー
No, no.
ない、ない
do not have?
ない?
Seriously?
マジ?
I thought I was the biggest fan,
俺が一番太いファンだと思ってさ、
It actually helps a lot.
実際にいっぱい助けられます
Make me a lot of fans.
いっぱいファンさせて
Are you pulling back a little?
ちょっと引いてる?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It doesn't matter if you look at it, you didn't say where you were looking at it.
見てって別にさ、 何処見ててとか言ってないのにさ、
Look there, it's proof that you're a little concerned, right?
そこ見てさ、 ちょっと気になってる証拠やでしょ?
actually.
実は
Won't you please let me down?
下出してくれない?
If you say you won't stream it anywhere, you're betraying your fans.
どこにもね、配信しないといえば 一応ファンを裏切ってるから、
It's really no good, right?
本当ダメでしょ?
Is it?
ですか?
You haven't done anything like this, have you?
こんな ことしてないでしょ?
Shall I apologize a little?
ちょっと謝ろうか!?
Let's apologize to the fans in front of the camera.
カメラの前でファンに謝っておこう
From now on, I'm going to do something naughty.
今から、エッチなことします
Say it while making peace.
ピースしながら言ってください
The fan beeps.
ファンにピー
Please say it while saying it.
ス しながら言ってください
I'm going to do a lot of naughty things from now on.
今からいっぱいエッチなことしちゃいます
It's no good, it's no good.
ダメじゃん、ダメじゃん
picture?
え?
what?
何?
I've already touched your nipples.
もう乳首触ってんだけど
Mom, please guide me and touch my nipples.
お母さん、自分で誘導して、乳首触って
Huh, there?
え、そこ?
There, here.
そこ、ここ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
soft.
柔らかい
Shiniri.
しんいり
Don't touch it?
触らない?
I can't touch it.
触 れない
13 hours left.
あと13時間もね
It's difficult.
難しいなぁ
It's a little see-through.
ちょっと透けてんじゃん
This is a bit naughty, isn't it?
ちょっとエッチいんだね、これ
Stretch your legs a little.
ちょっと足伸ばしてみて
Your feet are beautiful.
足綺麗だね
what up?
どうした?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだ
I'll touch you a lot.
いっぱい触ってあげる
It might be a hand.
手やかもしれない
Actually a little
実はちょっと
I want to take a tantsu and take a closer look, so I'll do it myself.
タ ンツ持ってよく見たいから、 自分でさ、
Hide it up.
隠し上げて
After all, Ainobu is white.
やっぱりアイノブって白なんだ
Hey, just try raising one leg.
ちょっとさ、足片子だけ上げてみて
Where is your foot hitting right now?
今足どこに当たってますか?
Is it difficult for one child to understand?
片子じゃわかりづらいか
One more time.
もう一回
It's boring.
つまらないです
So, can I have you do a double piece?
そこでさ、ダブルピースしてもらっていい?
Fingers, look.
指、ほら
What do you want to do?
よどうしたい?
refer to.
指
Where does it feel good to be touched?
どこ触られたら気持ちいいの?
Where is it?
どこだろう?
But around here.
でも、ここらへん
Kuritorisa is being touched.
くりとりさ、触られてますって
Ask me to take it off.
脱いでもらって
Fresh clothes.
生着替え
Idol student changing clothes.
アイドル生着替え
The style is really nice.
スタイルめっちゃいいね
Since I usually give lessons,
普段レッスンとかしちゃうだけあってね、
It's just because I exercise.
運動しちゃうだけあって
It's tight.
引き締まってるね
Well, let's take a closer look.
じゃあちょっと近くで見るね
This is a bit of a fetish, and I like being next to plastic girls.
これさ、ちょっと性癖があって、 プラの子の横は好きなのよ
I like the side.
横が好きで
Isn't it big?
大きいじゃない?
big?
大きい?
Spread your legs.
足広げて
Isn't that pretty beautiful?
あれ、結構美感?
You don't need underwear.
下着なっていらないよね
It's so beautiful
めっちゃ綺麗だよ
Na.
な
It just looks so beautiful.
それ だけ綺麗かかるね
I don't need it, but my bones are soft.
いらないけど、骨柔らかいの
い らないけど、骨柔らかいの
It smells really bad.
めっちゃ臭くて
Both stink.
どっちも臭い
It's a lesson table, right?
レッスン台でしょ?
I understand.
わかるよ
odor?
臭い?
Because he's a pervert.
変態なんだからさ
I stopped it on my own, so for a while.
勝手にやめちゃったから、 ちょっと
Pen.
ペ ン
Because I want to touch you underneath
下触りたいから
difference.
さ
Sit down and turn your head over here.
座 ってさ、ちょっとこっち頭にしてさ、
Goron came out diagonally.
斜めにゴロン出てきて
I just said it.
さっき言っちゃったんだよね
The back side of Ainoro.
アイノロの裏側
Tighten it up a bit.
ちょっと締めて
Just now, Clinic Placer.
さっきさ、 クリニックプラサー
How are you doing it?
どうやってんの?
Can you put your elbows there?
そこで肘つける?
I got really involved.
めっちゃ絡みつかんだ
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいいね
I just put my finger in it.
指入れただけだもん
It makes me so excited.
なんかさ、キュンキュンしてね
Awesome, amazing, amazing.
すごいすごいすごい
Raise your feet.
足上げて
While peace.
ピースしながら
Have you ever been hit by one yourself?
自分でさ、ひられてみたことある?
yes.
はい
It's my first time.
初めてだね
There's nothing to put in
チンチン入れるのがない
is.
です
It looks like it's going to ring out.
か んやみで鳴らそっか
It's difficult, isn't it?
難しいよね
Not though.
ないけど
I won't stop though.
やめないけどね
What's going on with your dick?
チンコどうなってる?
fine.
元気
a,
あ、
Okay.
いい よ
You can take a look.
ちらってみてもいいよ
I glanced at it.
ちらってみちゃった
copper?
どう?
This chin chin.
このチンチン
Was it there?
あったか?
Try bringing your face closer.
顔近づけてみて
Moshiwa.
もしわ
painful?
苦しい?
You can't get used to it.
慣れないよね
Can I put that in?
それ入れていい?
Can I come in?
入れていい?
Cats too.
猫も
A cat is a cat too, but how much should I include?
猫も猫なんだけどさ、 何まで入れていいかな?
not good.
良くない
picture?
え?
not good?
良くない?
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Reflect it.
反射してよ
Please wear a hair tire just for today.
今日だけ髪タイヤをしてよ
I'll really support you.
めっちゃ応援するから
め っちゃ応援するから
Put a tire on your head.
頭タイヤをしてよ
No?
ダメ?
What if I want to take it outside?
外に出すんだったら?
Outside.
外に
I'll put it out right away then.
じゃあすぐ出すから
I don't have much time to take it out and put it in right away, so I take it outside.
すぐ出して入れる時間少なくて、 外に出すから
Is that okay?
だったらいい?
Put your hand between my legs.
手を俺の足の間に入れて
Put it between your legs.
足の間に入れて
Spread your legs.
足広げて
Now, stand on your feet and bring your hands in front of you.
じゃあ、 足つきながら、 手を前に持ってきて
Clinging to mom's, mom's hand.
ママの、 ママの手にくっついて
Rub it into the hair on your upper body.
上半身の毛筋にグーってして
Can I take it out?
出していい?
You can't take it out.
出してダメだよ
why?
なんで?
It's coming out.
出るね
I'll put it out.
出すね
It's not outside.
外じゃないの
He has a beard.
髭ついてる
If you make a mistake, you're in trouble.
間違えたらヤバい
That's dangerous.
ヤ バ い
Really.
本当に
I took it out today and it was crazy.
今日出したらヤバかった
I wonder if it's dangerous.
ヤバいかな
Did you know that sperm was coming out inside?
中で精子出てるの分かった?
Will you clean it up?
綺麗にしてくれる?
I'll talk to you a little later.
ちょっと後で話すとして
Shall I go take a quick shower?
一回ちょっとシャワー浴びに行こうか
Then peace there.
じゃあそこでピースして
I was creampied by an idol's pussy.
ア イドルおまんこに中出しされちゃいました